Frank J. Becker Papers
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Subject Files, 1953-1964; 1974; nam_apap224-1; 15.04 cubic ft.
  - Education, Federal Aid, 1963; nam_apap224-1_165 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Education, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_166 (Box 6, Folder 13-14)
  - Education, Legislation, 1964; nam_apap224-1_167 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Federal Aviation Agency, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_168 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Federal Communications Commission, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_169 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Federal Power Commission, Department, 1964; nam_apap224-1_170 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Federal Trade Commission, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_171 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Flight Engineer Dispute, 1961; nam_apap224-1_172 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Flight Engineer Dispute, 1961; nam_apap224-1_173 (Flat-file 3)
  - Football Tickets, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_174 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Foreign Affairs, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_175 (Box 6, Folder 22-25)
  - Foreign Affairs, Legislation, Cuba, 1963; nam_apap224-1_176 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Foreign Affairs, Legislation, Israel, 1963; nam_apap224-1_177 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Foreign Affairs, Legislation, 1964; nam_apap224-1_178 (Box 6, Folder 28-29)
  - Foreign Affairs, Legislation, Cuba, 1964; nam_apap224-1_179 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Foreign Claims Settlement Commission, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_180 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - General Services Administration, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_181 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Government Operations Committee, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_182 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Government Operations Committee, Legislation, 1964; nam_apap224-1_183 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Hafner, Harold R., Correspondence, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_184 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_185 (Box 7, Folder 6-7)
  - Health, Welfare, Education, Krebiozen, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_186 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - House Administration, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_187 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - House Administration, Legislation, 1964; nam_apap224-1_188 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Housing and Home Finance Agency, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_189 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Iceland, 1963; nam_apap224-1_190 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Interior, Department, 1961-1964; nam_apap224-1_191 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_192 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs, Legislation, 1964; nam_apap224-1_193 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1963; nam_apap224-1_194 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_195 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - International Communism Briefing, 1961 October 07; nam_apap224-1_196 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - International Communism, Attachment # 1, 1960; nam_apap224-1_197 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - International Communism, Attachment # 2, 1961 September; nam_apap224-1_198 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - International Communism, Attachment # 3, 1959; nam_apap224-1_199 (Box 7, Folder 21-22)
  - International Communism, Attachment # 4, 1960 May 10; nam_apap224-1_200 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - International Communism, Attachment # 5, 1960 February; nam_apap224-1_201 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - International Communism, Attachment # 6, 1961; nam_apap224-1_202 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - International Communism, Attachment # 7, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-1_203 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_204 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee, 1963; nam_apap224-1_205 (Box 7, Folder 28-29)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_206 (Box 7, Folder 30-31)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee (Humane Treatment), Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_207 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee, Legislation, 1964; nam_apap224-1_208 (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
  - Jobs, A-H, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_209 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Jobs, L-M, O-P, 1964; nam_apap224-1_210 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Jobs, Pages, R-S, 1964; nam_apap224-1_211 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Jobs, Summer, 1964; nam_apap224-1_212 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Jobs, T, 1964; nam_apap224-1_213 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Jobs, W, 1964; nam_apap224-1_214 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Joint Committee on Atomic Energy, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_215 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Joint Committee on Atomic Energy, Legislation, 1964; nam_apap224-1_216 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Judiciary Committee, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_217 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Judiciary Committee, Legislation, 1964; nam_apap224-1_218 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Judiciary Committee, Legislation, Civil Rights, 1963; nam_apap224-1_219 (Box 8, Folder 15-21)
  - Justice, Department, 1963; nam_apap224-1_220 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Justice, Department, Immigration and Naturalization, 1963; nam_apap224-1_221 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Labor, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_222 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Labor, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_223 (Box 8, Folder 25-26)
  - Labor, Legislation, 1964; nam_apap224-1_224 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Legislation, General Correspondence about 88th Congress, 1963; nam_apap224-1_225 (Box 9, Folder 2-3)
  - Legislation, General Correspondence about 88th Congress, 1964; nam_apap224-1_226 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Library of Congress, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_227 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Materials about Thaddeus Kosciusczko and 4H Clubs, 1961; nam_apap224-1_228 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Marine Corps, 1964; nam_apap224-1_229 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_230 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries, Legislation, 1964; nam_apap224-1_231 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Monroe Doctrine, Petition of Preservation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_232 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Nassau County, Bellmore Training Center, Army, 1957; nam_apap224-1_233 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Nassau County, Bellmore Training Center, Army, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-1_234 (Box 9, Folder 12-13)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Adm., Department, 1961-1964; nam_apap224-1_235 (Box 9, Folder 14-15)
  - National Science Foundation, Department, 1964; nam_apap224-1_236 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Navy, Contracts, Joseph A. Boga, 1964; nam_apap224-1_237 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Navy, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_238 (Box 9, Folder 18-19)
  - Navy, New York Naval Shipyard, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_239 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - News Clippings, Frank J. Becker, 1954; nam_apap224-1_240 (Box 9, Folder 21-22)
  - News Clippings, Frank J. Becker, 1955; nam_apap224-1_241 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - News Clippings, Frank J. Becker, 1956; nam_apap224-1_242 (Box 9, Folder 24-25)
  - News Clippings, Frank J. Becker, 1957; nam_apap224-1_243 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - News Clippings, Frank J. Becker, 1958; nam_apap224-1_244 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - News Clippings, Frank J. Becker, 1959; nam_apap224-1_245 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - News Clippings, Frank J. Becker, 1960; nam_apap224-1_246 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - News Clippings, Frank J. Becker, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-1_247 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Newsletter, General, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-1_248 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1962; nam_apap224-1_249 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
  - Newsletter, 1961 February; nam_apap224-1_250 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, Booklets Sent to Enclosed, No Letter, 1961 February; nam_apap224-1_251 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1961 February; nam_apap224-1_252 (Box 10, Folder 5-11)
  - Newsletter, 1961 November 08; nam_apap224-1_253 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1961 November 08; nam_apap224-1_254 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Newsletter, 1961 November 30; nam_apap224-1_255 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1961 November 30; nam_apap224-1_256 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Newsletter, 1961 December 10; nam_apap224-1_257 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1961 December 10; nam_apap224-1_258 (Box 10, Folder 17-18)
  - Newsletter, 1961 December 21; nam_apap224-1_259 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1961 December 21; nam_apap224-1_260 (Box 10, Folder 20-21)
  - Newsletter, 1962 January 31; nam_apap224-1_261 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1962 January 31; nam_apap224-1_262 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Newsletter, 1962 February 13; nam_apap224-1_263 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1962 February 13; nam_apap224-1_264 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Newsletter, 1962 April 17; nam_apap224-1_265 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1962 April 17; nam_apap224-1_266 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Newsletter, 1962 April 20; nam_apap224-1_267 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1962 April 20; nam_apap224-1_268 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Newsletter, 1962 September 17; nam_apap224-1_269 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1962 September 17; nam_apap224-1_270 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Newsletter, 1962 October 04; nam_apap224-1_271 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Newsletter, General Correspondence, 1962 October 04; nam_apap224-1_272 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Newsday Letter, 1963 August; nam_apap224-1_273 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Newsletter, Washington Report, 1963; nam_apap224-1_274 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - News Releases, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-1_275 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - News Releases, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1955; nam_apap224-1_276 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - News Releases, Harry Hart, 1955; nam_apap224-1_277 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - News Releases, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1956; nam_apap224-1_278 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - News Releases, Harry Hart, 1956; nam_apap224-1_279 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - News Releases, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1957; nam_apap224-1_280 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - News Releases, Harry Hart, 1957; nam_apap224-1_281 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - News Releases, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1958; nam_apap224-1_282 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - News Releases, Harry Hart, 1958; nam_apap224-1_283 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - News Releases, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1959; nam_apap224-1_284 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - News Releases, General Correspondence, 1959; nam_apap224-1_285 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - News Releases, Harry Hart, 1959; nam_apap224-1_286 (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
  - News Releases, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1960; nam_apap224-1_287 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - News Releases, Harry Hart, 1960; nam_apap224-1_288 (Box 11, Folder 9-10)
  - News Releases, 1961; nam_apap224-1_289 (Box 11, Folder 11-12)
  - News Releases, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1961; nam_apap224-1_290 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - News Releases, Washington Reports, 1961; nam_apap224-1_291 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - News Releases, 1962; nam_apap224-1_292 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - News Releases, 1963; nam_apap224-1_293 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - News Releases, Long Island Newspapers, 1963; nam_apap224-1_294 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - News Releases, 1964; nam_apap224-1_295 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Oral History Interview with Frank J. Becker, 1974 March 17; nam_apap224-1_296 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Panama Canal, Dept., 1964; nam_apap224-1_297 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Peace Corps, 1964; nam_apap224-1_298 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Personal Affairs Institute, 1962; nam_apap224-1_299 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Post Office, Department, 1962-1964; nam_apap224-1_300 (Box 11, Folder 23-24)
  - Post Office, Fifth District, 1963; nam_apap224-1_301 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Post Office, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_302 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Post Office, Legislation, 1964; nam_apap224-1_303 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Post Office Cases, Atlantic Beach, 1953; 1956-1958; 1960-1963; nam_apap224-1_304 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - Post Office Cases, Baldwin, 1955; 1957; 1960-1963; nam_apap224-1_305 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Post Office Cases, Bellmore, 1955; 1960-1962; nam_apap224-1_306 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Post Office Cases, East Rockaway, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-1_307 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Post Office Cases, Freeport, 1963; nam_apap224-1_308 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Post Office Cases, Hewlett, 1962-1964; nam_apap224-1_309 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Post Office Cases, Island Park, 1960; 1962; nam_apap224-1_310 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Post Office Cases, Lawrence, 1957-1960; 1963; nam_apap224-1_311 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Post Office Cases, Lido Beach, 1958; 1961-1963; nam_apap224-1_312 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Post Office Cases, Long Beach, 1964; nam_apap224-1_313 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Post Office Cases, Malverne, 1959-1963; nam_apap224-1_314 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Post Office Cases, Merrick, 1961-1963; nam_apap224-1_315 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Post Office Cases, Nassau County, General, 1961-1963; nam_apap224-1_316 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Post Office Cases, Nassau County, General, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_317 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Post Office Cases, North Merrick, 1953; 1955-1957; 1960-1963; nam_apap224-1_318 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Post Office Cases, Obscene Mail, 1963; nam_apap224-1_319 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Post Office Cases, Oceanside, 1953-1954; 1957-1963; nam_apap224-1_320 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Post Office Cases, Rockville Centre, 1961; 1963; nam_apap224-1_321 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Post Office Cases, Roosevelt, 1962; nam_apap224-1_322 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Post Office Cases, Valley Stream, 1956-1964; nam_apap224-1_323 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Post Office Cases, Wantagh, 1955-1957; 1959; 1961; nam_apap224-1_324 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Post Office Cases, Woodmere, 1962-1963; nam_apap224-1_325 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Post Office Cases, Woodmere/Valley Stream, 1957-1963; nam_apap224-1_326 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Prayer Amendment, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_327 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Presidential Messages, 1963; nam_apap224-1_328 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Public Works, Jones and Rockaway Inlet, 1963; nam_apap224-1_329 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Public Works, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_330 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Public Works, Legislation, 1964; nam_apap224-1_331 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Questionnaire, Army Reserve, Undated; nam_apap224-1_332 (Box 12, Folder 30-31)
  - Questionnaire, Frank J. Becker, 1962 April; nam_apap224-1_333 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Reports, 1960; nam_apap224-1_334 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Reports, 1959-1960; 1962; nam_apap224-1_335 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Republic Aviation Briefing, 1963; nam_apap224-1_336 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Requests, A, 1964; nam_apap224-1_337 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Requests, Agriculture Yearbook, 1963; nam_apap224-1_338 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Requests, Agriculture Yearbook, 1964; nam_apap224-1_339 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Requests, B, 1964; nam_apap224-1_340 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Requests, C, 1964; nam_apap224-1_341 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Requests, Calendars, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_342 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Requests, Celodyne Corporations, 1963; nam_apap224-1_343 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Requests, D, 1964; nam_apap224-1_344 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Requests, E, 1964; nam_apap224-1_345 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Requests, F, 1964; nam_apap224-1_346 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Requests, G, 1964; nam_apap224-1_347 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Requests, H, 1964; nam_apap224-1_348 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Requests, I, 1964; nam_apap224-1_349 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Requests, Intern Programs, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_350 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Requests, J, 1964; nam_apap224-1_351 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Requests, K, 1964; nam_apap224-1_352 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Requests, L, 1964; nam_apap224-1_353 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Requests, M, 1964; nam_apap224-1_354 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Requests, N, 1964; nam_apap224-1_355 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Requests, O, 1964; nam_apap224-1_356 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Requests, P, 1964; nam_apap224-1_357 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Requests, Publications, 1964; nam_apap224-1_358 (Box 13, Folder 22-23)
  - Requests, Q, 1964; nam_apap224-1_359 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Requests, R, 1964; nam_apap224-1_360 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Requests, S, 1964; nam_apap224-1_361 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Requests, T, 1964; nam_apap224-1_362 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Requests, V, 1964; nam_apap224-1_363 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Requests, W, 1964; nam_apap224-1_364 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Requests, Warren Commission Reports, 1964; nam_apap224-1_365 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Requests, Z, 1964; nam_apap224-1_366 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Rules, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_367 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Rules, Legislation, 1964; nam_apap224-1_368 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Science and Aeronautics, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_369 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission, Department, 1963; nam_apap224-1_370 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Selective Service System, Department, 1963; nam_apap224-1_371 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Small Business Administration, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_372 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Small Business Administration, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_373 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Social Security, Al Levine, 1963; nam_apap224-1_374 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Social Security, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_375 (Box 13, Folder 40-41)
  - Speeches, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-1_376 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Speeches, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1955; nam_apap224-1_377 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Speeches, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1956; nam_apap224-1_378 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Speeches, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1957; nam_apap224-1_379 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Speeches, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1958; nam_apap224-1_380 (Box 14, Folder 5-6)
  - Speeches, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1959; nam_apap224-1_381 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Speeches, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1960; nam_apap224-1_382 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Speeches, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1961; nam_apap224-1_383 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Speeches, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1962; nam_apap224-1_384 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Speeches, Extra, Free Enterprise vs. The Welfare State, 1962; nam_apap224-1_385 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Speeches, Frank J. Becker, Copies, 1963; nam_apap224-1_386 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - State, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_387 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - State, Department, Agency of International Development, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_388 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - State, Department, Passports, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_389 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Statements, Frank J. Becker, 1961; nam_apap224-1_390 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Statements, Frank J. Becker, 1962; nam_apap224-1_391 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Tariff Commission, Department, 1963; nam_apap224-1_392 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Treasury, Department, 1962-1964; nam_apap224-1_393 (Box 14, Folder 19-20)
  - Trips, Fort Dix, Undated; nam_apap224-1_394 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Un-American Activities, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_395 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - United Nations, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_396 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Veterans Administration, Department, 1963; nam_apap224-1_397 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Veterans Affairs, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_398 (Box 14, Folder 25-26)
  - Veterans Affairs, Legislation, 1964; nam_apap224-1_399 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Veterans Committee, Letters, Discharge Petitions, 1963; nam_apap224-1_400 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Visitors, 1963 January-1963 June; nam_apap224-1_401 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
  - Visitors, 1963 July-1963 December; nam_apap224-1_402 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Visitors, 1964 January-1964 June; nam_apap224-1_403 (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
  - Washington Report, 1961; nam_apap224-1_404 (Box 15, Folder 6-7)
  - Washington Report, 1962; nam_apap224-1_405 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Washington Report, 1963; nam_apap224-1_406 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Washington Report, 1964; nam_apap224-1_407 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Waterways, 1953-1957; nam_apap224-1_408 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Ways and Means, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_409 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Ways and Means, Legislation, 1964; nam_apap224-1_410 (Box 16, Folder 6-7)
  - Ways and Means, Legislation, Medical Care, 1963; nam_apap224-1_411 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Ways and Means, Legislation, Medical Care, 1964; nam_apap224-1_412 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Ways and Means, Legislation, Social Security, 1963; nam_apap224-1_413 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Ways and Means, Legislation, Tariffs, 1963; nam_apap224-1_414 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Ways and Means, Legislation, Tax, Frank J. Becker Speech, 1963; nam_apap224-1_415 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - White House, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_416 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - White House, President Kennedy's Assassination, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_417 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1953-1964; nam_apap224-2; 2.4 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically by correspondence type.
  As a Congressman, Frank Becker interacted with his constituents continually, the most common method being through correspondence. The series documents three specific groups of individuals that Becker corresponded with: Immigrants (stamped IC on the paperwork), Servicemen (stamped SM on the paperwork), and Veterans (stamped VC on the paperwork). These are only a few of many groups of people Becker interacted with. However, Becker elected to keep this correspondence separate and the archivists maintained this order. Additionally, interspersed throughout the series are copies of original public laws, a questionnaire, and newspaper clippings.
  - Immigration, A, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Immigration, A, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Immigration, A, 1957; nam_apap224-2_3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Immigration, A, 1958; nam_apap224-2_4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Immigration, A, 1959; nam_apap224-2_5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Immigration, A, 1960; nam_apap224-2_6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Immigration, A, 1961; nam_apap224-2_7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Immigration, A, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-2_8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Immigration, A, 1963; nam_apap224-2_9 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Immigration, Allison, Calvin, Carmen, 1955-1958; nam_apap224-2_10 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Immigration, B - [RESTRICTED], 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Immigration, B, 1954-1956; nam_apap224-2_12 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Immigration, B, 1957; nam_apap224-2_13 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Immigration, B, 1958; nam_apap224-2_14 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Immigration, B, 1959; nam_apap224-2_15 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Immigration, B, 1960; nam_apap224-2_16 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Immigration, B, 1961; nam_apap224-2_17 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Immigration, B, 1962; nam_apap224-2_18 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Immigration, B, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-2_19 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Immigration, Bedard, A., 1955; nam_apap224-2_20 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Immigration, C, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_21 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Immigration, C, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_22 (Box 1, Folder 0)
  - Immigration, C, 1957; nam_apap224-2_23 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Immigration, C, 1958; nam_apap224-2_24 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Immigration, C, 1959; nam_apap224-2_25 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Immigration, C, 1960; nam_apap224-2_26 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Immigration, C, 1960-1962; nam_apap224-2_27 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Immigration, C, 1961; nam_apap224-2_28 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Immigration, C, 1961-1963; nam_apap224-2_29 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Immigration, C, 1963; nam_apap224-2_30 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Immigration, D, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-2_31 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Immigration, D, 1955-1959; nam_apap224-2_32 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Immigration, D, 1956; nam_apap224-2_33 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Immigration, D, 1956-1957; nam_apap224-2_34 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Immigration, D, 1957-1958; nam_apap224-2_35 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Immigration, D, 1960-1961; nam_apap224-2_36 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Immigration, D, 1962; nam_apap224-2_37 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Immigration, D, 1963; nam_apap224-2_38 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Immigration, E, 1953; nam_apap224-2_39 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Immigration, E, 1955-1956; nam_apap224-2_40 (Box 2, Folder 16)